{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074768390","data":{"timestamp":" 947074768390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074777760","data":{"timestamp":" 947074777760"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074779326","data":{"timestamp":" 947074779326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074782498","data":{"timestamp":" 947074782497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074784051","data":{"timestamp":" 947074784051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074785332","data":{"timestamp":" 947074785332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" START_KAROTI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074789490","data":{"timestamp":" 947074789490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074791080","data":{"timestamp":" 947074791080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074799927","data":{"timestamp":" 947074799927"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074801496","data":{"timestamp":" 947074801496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074808038","data":{"timestamp":" 947074808037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074809609","data":{"timestamp":" 947074809609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074814558","data":{"timestamp":" 947074814558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074816121","data":{"timestamp":" 947074816121"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074819487","data":{"timestamp":" 947074819487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074821043","data":{"timestamp":" 947074821043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074824444","data":{"timestamp":" 947074824444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074826011","data":{"timestamp":" 947074826011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074829338","data":{"timestamp":" 947074829338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074830727","data":{"timestamp":" 947074830727"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074831127","data":{"timestamp":" 947074831126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074834528","data":{"timestamp":" 947074834528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074838527","data":{"timestamp":" 947074838526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074840092","data":{"timestamp":" 947074840091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" NYANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074844962","data":{"timestamp":" 947074844961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyanya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074846525","data":{"timestamp":" 947074846525"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074870390","data":{"timestamp":" 947074870390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074871046","data":{"timestamp":" 947074871045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074871186","data":{"timestamp":" 947074871185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 3c38d2cc-833a-4021-808c-5de3e8f32443"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" maji"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074883735","data":{"timestamp":" 947074883734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074890603","data":{"timestamp":" 947074890603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" viazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074892144","data":{"timestamp":" 947074892144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074898195","data":{"timestamp":" 947074898195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" START_EMBE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074901847","data":{"timestamp":" 947074901847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074903429","data":{"timestamp":" 947074903429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" KAROTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074908736","data":{"timestamp":" 947074908735"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karoti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAROTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074910308","data":{"timestamp":" 947074910308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074914364","data":{"timestamp":" 947074914364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074915944","data":{"timestamp":" 947074915943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074920298","data":{"timestamp":" 947074920298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074921865","data":{"timestamp":" 947074921864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074928241","data":{"timestamp":" 947074928241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitumbua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074929807","data":{"timestamp":" 947074929807"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074933830","data":{"timestamp":" 947074933830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" START_UGALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074942613","data":{"timestamp":" 947074942612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074944175","data":{"timestamp":" 947074944174"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" MBOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074951235","data":{"timestamp":" 947074951235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mboga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBOGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074952846","data":{"timestamp":" 947074952846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074955884","data":{"timestamp":" 947074955884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALI"," userResponse":" WALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074957470","data":{"timestamp":" 947074957470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074965952","data":{"timestamp":" 947074965952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074967312","data":{"timestamp":" 947074967311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074967537","data":{"timestamp":" 947074967537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074982145","data":{"timestamp":" 947074982145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074982257","data":{"timestamp":" 947074982257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 06cd54e6-4543-4513-bec2-074961f68e74"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_pic.cat-food.rand.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" samaki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074994216","data":{"timestamp":" 947074994215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074994447","data":{"timestamp":" 947074994447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074995415","data":{"timestamp":" 947074995415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074996694","data":{"timestamp":" 947074996694"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947074999612","data":{"timestamp":" 947074999611"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075000479","data":{"timestamp":" 947075000478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075000798","data":{"timestamp":" 947075000797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075002031","data":{"timestamp":" 947075002031"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075005608","data":{"timestamp":" 947075005608"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075006592","data":{"timestamp":" 947075006592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075006846","data":{"timestamp":" 947075006846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075007789","data":{"timestamp":" 947075007789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075010665","data":{"timestamp":" 947075010665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075011699","data":{"timestamp":" 947075011699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075012172","data":{"timestamp":" 947075012172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075016667","data":{"timestamp":" 947075016667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075016786","data":{"timestamp":" 947075016786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 1ce55d64-7f1c-4bbf-b75f-5ff22fe573b8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075028430","data":{"timestamp":" 947075028429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075034520","data":{"timestamp":" 947075034520"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075036274","data":{"timestamp":" 947075036274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075038537","data":{"timestamp":" 947075038537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAITWA"," userResponse":" ANAITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075038847","data":{"timestamp":" 947075038847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BI"," userResponse":" BI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075039467","data":{"timestamp":" 947075039467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaitwa Bi Simu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMU"," userResponse":" SIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075044114","data":{"timestamp":" 947075044114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" START_MWANGALIE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075045602","data":{"timestamp":" 947075045602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" START_MWANGALIE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075047397","data":{"timestamp":" 947075047397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075049635","data":{"timestamp":" 947075049635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947075050164","data":{"timestamp":" 947075050164"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_151914"," gameId":" 83e51036-2f28-4111-b748-fdf1276a6af6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwangalie!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGALIE"," userResponse":" MWANGALIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}